Won’t leave
떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
자자스 자자스 나사타나다 자자스
-She summoned me, the evil god. -Evil god!
- 저 애가 소환한 난 악마다 - 악마다!
-I gotta kill her or else -What?
저 애를 죽이지 않으면 뭐?
-I can’t go back to Hell! -Sister...
지옥에 갈 수가 없어 자매여...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw!
그래! 그래! 그래! 죽음과 살기 위해, 전기톱으로 싸워야지!
If you go too far,
네가 막 나가면
I’ll slice you up completely!
널 완전히 썰어버릴 거야!
Your halo! Must get it back!
네 후광을 반드시 되찾아야지!
-Never miss a chance -Hey, seriously?
기회를 절대 놓치지 마 정말 그럴 거야?
-To attack her from behind! -You’re so mean.
뒤에서 공격하려고? 넌 못됐어
I’ll never give up.
난 절대 포기 안 해
Yurine, you’re off your guard!
유리네, 방심하고 있군!
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
지금이다! 로열코펜하겐으로 끝내주지!
Huh? What? I missed...
어, 뭐지? 실패다...
Can’t leave Earth
지구를 떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
But until then,
하지만 그때까진
-let’s all have fun together! -Yeah!
모두 같이 놀자! 신난다!
Dinner's ready!
저녁 먹자!
I'm serving curry tonight.
오늘 저녁은 카레야
Nice, pork cutlet curry.
돈가스 카레네, 좋다
-Let's eat. -Let's eat!
- 잘 먹겠습니다 - 잘 먹겠습니다!
-All done.
- 다 먹었다
Curry for dinner, huh? Looks good!
저녁이 카레야? 맛있겠다!
THE NIGHT AFTER
'그다음 날 밤'
Curry for dinner again!
오늘 저녁도 카레다!
It's hamburger steak curry tonight.
오늘은 함박스테이크 카레군
Curry's best on the second day.
카레는 이틀째 제일 맛있지
-Let's eat. -Let's eat!
- 잘 먹겠습니다 - 잘 먹겠습니다!
-All done. -All done!
- 다 먹었다
THE NIGHT AFTER. AGAIN.
'그다음 날 밤 또'
That's right! It's curry three nights in a row!
맞아! 3일 연속으로 카레다!
That's a bit excessive...
조금 지나치군
We shouldn't be doing this, even for just 20 minutes.
20분 만이라도 이러지 말자
Not to worry.
걱정하지 마
This is the last time.
이게 마지막이야
Still, it's three days in a row...
하지만 3일씩이나 계속...
Rock, paper...
가위 바위
-Scissors.
- 보
I didn't mean to win.
이기려던 게 아닌데
Jashin-chan, you just won
사신짱, 네가 이겼어
the privilege of getting out the mayo.
마요네즈를 가져올 특권을 주지
Yes! Right away!
네! 즉시 시행하죠!
-Here you go. -Thanks.
- 여기 있어 - 고마워
YURINE
'유리네'
Is-- Is that for your curry?
그... 그걸 카레에 넣으려고?
Of course.
물론이지
Mayo on curry?
카레 위에 마요네즈를?
That's sacrilege!
이건 신성모독이야!
They really go well together.
맛이 아주 잘 어울려
Here, try it.
자, 먹어 봐
-It's delicious! -See?
- 맛있다! - 그렇지?
But why? How is that possible?
하지만 어떻게? 어떻게 그게 가능하지?
Can't go wrong with mayo.
마요네즈는 다 잘 어울려
That didn't answer my question. Nevertheless, it's good.
내 질문에 답한 건 아니지만 어찌 됐든 맛있다
No doubt about it.
그건 확실해
Curry and mayo, the winning combo.
카레와 마요네즈는 환상적인 조합이군
No doubt!
분명해!
That's it!
그래!
-I'm making curry again tomorrow! -Again?
- 난 내일도 카레 요리를 할 거야 - 또?
Look at that.
어디 보자
So, you can buy these things on Amazon.
그러니까 이런 걸 아마존에서 살 수 있구나
You're really making curry again?
정말 또 카레를 만드는 거야?
Yup. It's chicken curry tonight.
응, 오늘 저녁은 치킨 카레야
If you power walk
힘차게 걸으면
I live five minutes away From the station.
역에서 5분 거리에 우리 집이 있지
The katar or chakram...
카타르하고 차크람 중에
Which do you think is sharper?
뭐가 더 날카로울까?
Hey.
얘
Are you listening to me?
내 말을 들은 거야?
What?
응?
She disappeared.
사라졌네
What's going on?
어떻게 된 거지?
What just happened?
방금 무슨 일이 일어난 거야?
Let me explain!
설명하죠!
While Jashin-chan was stirring the curry,
사신짱이 카레를 젓고 있을 때
she unintentionally formed a magic circle
아무 생각 없이 마법의 원을 만들었고
and sacrificed the chicken!
닭을 제물로 바쳤습니다
Furthermore, her random song matched up with the spell that opened the gates to the other dimension.
게다가 그냥 부른 그 노래가 어우러져 다른 차원으로 가는 문을 열었죠
Five minutes away From the station
역에서 5분 거리에
Jashin-chan was sucked into a warp!
사신짱은 워프로 빨려 들어간 겁니다
Where am I?
여긴 어디지?
Looks familiar, but...
낯설진 않은데...
The entrance to Hell!
지옥 입구잖아?
Welcome to Hell Free parking available in 666 miles
'지옥 방문 환영 666m 가면 무료 주차'
How did stirring the curry get me here?
카레 휘젓기로 어떻게 여길 온 거지?
Maybe...!
혹시...?
The kitchen exploded...
부엌이 폭파돼서
BANG
'펑'
And killed Yurine?
유리네가 죽었나?
Oh, no!
안 돼!
No, if that's the case, I'd be dead too.
아니지, 그랬다면 나도 죽었겠지
I don't get what happened.
무슨 일인지 전혀 모르겠군
But if all the conditions aren't met,
조건이 맞지 않으면
I'm just gonna get turned away.
날 다시 돌려보낼 거야
Hey, she looks like Jashin-chan, all grown up.
이봐, 저 여자는 어른이 된 사신짱처럼 생겼어
Only the fact that she's half-viper. Otherwise, not at all.
저 여자가 반쪽 독사란 것 말곤 전혀 안 똑같아
She's identical to you! She must be a relative.
너랑 똑같아! 네 친척인가 봐
Tiny Medusa, Minos...
어린 메두사와 미노스
And me!
그리고 나다!
Seems like she knows us.
저 사람이 우리를 아나 봐
See? She's a relative.
봤지? 네 친척이야
Are you my relative?
우리 친척이에요?
Where are you from?
어디서 온 거죠?
I was cooking in the human world just a minute ago. Before I knew it, I was here.
방금 인간 세계에서 요리를 했는데 나도 모르게 여기로 왔어
The human world?
인간 세계요?
Isn't the human world completely vacant because of the great flood?
인간 세계는 대홍수로 완전히 쓸려가지 않았나요?
The great flood...? The one from 7000 years ago?
대홍수...? 7,000년 전에 났던 거?
Noah!
노아!
Does that mean I went back in time?
그럼 내가 과거로 온 거야?
So, you're saying that you're Jashin-chan from the future?
당신이 미래에서 온 사신짱이란 건가요?
I'm sure you don't believe it.
믿기 힘들겠지
I believe you.
전 당신을 믿어요
Your eyes don't lie.
당신 눈은 거짓말을 안 해요
Medusa, as adorable as you are,
메두사, 넌 사랑스럽지만
don't let some fool deceive you.
바보에게 속지 마라
-Hey, miss! -Yeah?
- 저기요, 언니! - 응?
What am I like in the future?
난 미래에선 어떻게 생겼어요?
That flat chest of yours
지금 그 밋밋한 가슴이
is about triple the size!
세 배로 커졌지!
Triple the size? That sounds powerful!
세 배요? 힘이 셀 거 같아요!
You are strong.
넌 아주 강해
But, not as strong as me.
나만큼은 아니지만
What about me?
저는요?
-You're always working. -Really?
- 넌 항상 일해 - 정말요?
One of the most wonderful inventions of the future is the ATM...
미래엔 ATM이라는 멋진 발명품이 있지...
Me! What about me?
나요! 난 어때요?
-This. -What?
- 여기 있잖아 - 네?
You're looking straight at it.
지금 보고 있다고
No way!
절대 안 돼!
I was planning on becoming a lot cooler!
난 훨씬 더 멋지게 될 계획이었어요!
In your dreams!
꿈 깨!
This is bad. I have no idea how to get back to the human world.
큰일 났다, 인간세계로 돌아갈 방법을 모르겠어
Leave that to us!
우리에게 맡겨요
We'll send you back with our secret ritual.
우리가 비밀 의식으로 돌려보내 줄게요
Curry's up!
카레가 나왔습니다!
DROPKICK ON MY DEVIL!
사신짱 드롭킥
Now that's some fiery curry.
불타는 매운맛 카레군
I remember this.
이거 기억난다
But it's not gonna work.
하지만 소용없을 거야
We tried so many times.
우리는 여러 번 시도했었지
We always failed.
항상 실패했어
Look, she disappeared.
봐봐, 사라졌다
Did it work?
효과가 있었나?
Did you wish really hard for her return?
그 여자를 보내려고 힘껏 빌었니?
-Nope! I was dreaming about dinner! -What?
- 아니! 저녁 먹을 상상했어 - 뭐?
I'm starving! I wonder what's for dinner tonight.
난 배고파 오늘 저녁은 뭘까 궁금해
I hope it's curry.
카레를 먹으면 좋겠다
Curry? That sounds good.
카레? 그거 먹고 싶다
-I love chicken curry. -Is she okay?
- 난 치킨 카레가 좋아 - 그 언니는 괜찮을까?
Beef curry's my favorite, hands down.
쇠고기 카레가 제일 맛있어 진짜로
-Hey, that makes you a cannibal. -Shut up.
- 넌 동족을 먹는 거야 - 조용히 해
DEVILISHLY DELICIOUS NAAN
'악마처럼 지독하게 맛있는 난'
Ouch.
아야
What?
어?
Finally, I'm back.
겨우 돌아왔다
Where in the world have you been?
대체 넌 어디 갔던 거지?
One minute, you're gone.
갑자기 사라지더니
Next thing you know, you're on the table
또 갑자기 식탁 위에 나타났지
destroying all the food.
밥을 다 망가뜨렸어
Did you know that curry stains are impossible to get out?
카레는 색이 안 빠지는 거 알아?
Amazon delivery!
아마존 택배요!
I just ordered a minute ago.
1분 전에 주문한 건데
And it's already here.
벌써 도착했네
Thank goodness for Prime.
고맙다, 프라임
They're both really sharp.
두 개 다 정말 날카롭다
I'm shocked you kept on eating dinner
네 눈앞에서 내가 사라졌는데
when I suddenly vanished in front of your eyes!
저녁을 먹다니 정말 충격이다!
Curry again?
또 카레니?
Looks good!
맛있겠다!
Patience is key when it comes to love and curry!
사랑과 카레는 인내가 필수다
August is almost over.
8월이 거의 다 끝났다
But it's still really hot.
그런데 아직도 너무 더워
Don't ignore me. Say something.
날 무시하는 거야? 무슨 말 좀 해
That shaved ice from the stand was awesome!
그 가판대 빙수는 정말 끝내줬어
I wanna eat shaved ice!
나 빙수 먹고 싶어!
Was there a shaved ice stand around here?
이 근처에 빙수 가게가 있었나?
Could that be it?
저거야?
SHAVED ICE
'빙수'
Come and enjoy some shaved ice!
어서 와서 빙수 드세요!
Hey, it's Yusa and Koji!
어이, 유사와 코지!
Hey, you two. How are you?
안녕, 너희구나 잘 있었어?
It was you guys.
너희들이야?
It's the off-season in Hell right now.
지옥은 비수기야
So we came out here to work.
그래서 일하려고 여길 왔지
-It's pretty good money. -What?
- 돈을 많이 벌어 - 뭐?
You get rich off shaved ice?
빙수 팔아서 부자가 된다고?
Jashin-chan...
사신짱...
They're only able to make profit because there's no overhead
얘들은 빙수와 시럽을 만들 때 경비가 안 드니까
in producing the ice and syrups.
이윤을 많이 남길 수 있는 거야
It won't be the same for you.
네가 하면 많이 못 벌어
Too late.
너무 늦었군
Brain freeze! That's cold!
뇌가 언다! 너무 차가워!
I'm gonna make a killing off shaved ice too!
나도 빙수로 떼돈 벌 거야!
If Yusa's selling theirs for 200 yen...
유사네가 200엔에 파니까
I'll sell it for 300!
난 300엔 받을 거야!
Dummy. They'll all go for the cheaper one.
멍청이, 사람들은 더 싼 곳으로 갈 거다
I'd like a melon one please!
멜론 맛 하나 주세요
-Sold! -No way.
- 팔렸다 - 설마
Here they come!
사람들이 온다!
This heat must be getting to everyone.
다들 더위 먹은 거야
This shaved ice machine is really inefficient.
이 빙수기는 정말 능률이 떨어져
They're able to produce ice in a split second.
쟤네들은 순식간에 얼음을 만들 수 있는데
Damn it! Those brats!
젠장! 저 자식들이!
I'll operate three machines, with hands and my tail!
내 손과 꼬리를 써서 기계 세 대를 동시에 돌릴 거야
Hilarious
웃긴다
Head pain caused by eating shaved ice is also called
빙수를 먹어서 생긴 두통을
an "ice cream" headache.
"아이스크림" 두통이라고 하죠
That's an official medical term.
공식 의학용어입니다
I scream after that first bite of shaved ice!
난 빙수를 처음 한입 먹은 후 비명을 지르죠
JASHIN SHAVED ICE
'사신 빙수'
It's completely dead now.
이젠 완전히 끝났네
They still have a huge line.
쟤네들은 아직도 줄을 길게 섰다
Damn you, Koji! I'll change your name to Mimori
못된 코지! 네 이름을 미모리로 바꿀 거야
so it's harder for you to establish character.
그래야 네가 캐릭터를 만들기 힘들지
That's a pretty obscure reference.
너무 모호한 말이다
Wow, it's so light!
이거 정말 가볍다
This is heavenly!
천상의 맛이야
How ironic, they're devils.
재미있군, 쟤들은 악마다
The cheap ice, flavored syrups,
싼 얼음에 향미 시럽
and toy-like shaved ice machine
장난감 같은 빙수기로는
can't compete with their light and powdery ice.
쟤들의 가볍고 분말 같은 얼음과 경쟁이 안 되지
I must obtain the best ingredient to win!
최고 재료를 구해서 반드시 이길 거야
I'm going on a quest for natural ice from Mount Fuji!
자연산 얼음을 얻는 임무를 수행하러 후지산으로 간다
The air is so thin.
공기가 희박하다
But I made it to the sacred place.
하지만 성지에 도착했다
I hope...
사신짱을
I find Jashin-chan soon.
곧 찾게 해주세요
Ice, ice, ice!
얼음, 얼음, 얼음!
I'm fully stocked.
충분히 모았다
Where did all that energy come from?
그 힘이 다 어디서 나온 거야?
To achieve the finest ice...
최상의 얼음을 만들기 위해서
I got a professional shaved ice machine and expensive syrups!
빙수 전문 기계와 비싼 시럽을 샀다
-Voila! -Where did you get the money?
- 봐봐 - 돈을 어디서 구했지?
Medusa, I bought all of this with your money
메두사, 이거 전부 네 돈으로 샀어
so I could win.
내가 이길 수 있을 거야
-Good luck. -She died?
- 행운을 빌어 - 쟤는 죽었어?
In order to bring Yusa and Koji down,
유사와 코지를 무너뜨리려면
I'm selling mine
내 빙수를
for only five yen!
단돈 5엔에 팔 거다!
You can kiss profit goodbye.
돈을 벌긴 틀렸군
I'll produce better-quality ice to beat them!
쟤들을 이기려면 더 품질 좋은 얼음을 만들어야 해
-That wasn't her initial objective. -Fluffy, fluffy ice!
- 원래 목적은 그게 아니지 - 솜털처럼 가벼운 얼음아
Yusa and Koji, you guys
유사와 코지, 너희 둘
are about to be annihilated!
내가 박살 낼 거야
Now, humans...
자, 인간들아
Come and buy the ultimate shaved ice!
최상의 빙수를 사러 와라
Not so fast, viper girl.
기다려, 독사 양
You don't have a permit to do business here.
여기서 장사해도 된다는 허가증이 있어?
A permit?
허가증?
We have our permit, of course.
우리는 당연히 있죠
PERMIT
'허가증'
You can't do business here.
여기서 팔면 안 돼
You'd better come with us.
우리를 따라오는 게 좋을 거다
I see you're half-viper...
반쪽 독사군
-but your upper half could make you rich. -What?
- 하지만 상반신으로 부자 되겠다 - 뭐?
Well, actually, I've got a viper fetish.
사실 내가 독사에 많이 끌려
I think she wants you to save her.
저 애는 네가 구해주길 바랄 거야
No, that's the "Don't worry, I've got this" look.
아니야, 저건 "됐어, 내가 처리할게"라는 표정이야
Come on over! It's hot and fresh!
어서 오세요! 뜨겁고 신선합니다
One please!
하나 주세요!
CURRY SHAVED ICE
'카레 빙수'
All right. That should do it.
좋아, 충분할 거야
Wow, this is heavy.
이거 정말 무겁다
I've got no stamina since I haven't been eating.
먹은 게 없어서 기운이 없다
Where did this random huge rock come from?
갑자기 어디서 이런 큰 돌이 떨어진 거지?
If only I had my halo, I could turn that into bread.
후광만 있다면 저걸 빵으로 만들 텐데
That's enough water for today and tomorrow.
오늘과 내일은 이 물로 충분해
How did that get ripped?
어떻게 찢어진 걸까?
Pekola, I found you.
페코라, 여기 있었어요?
You're the angel apprentice.
넌 수습 천사?
That's me, Poporon.
나 포포롱이에요
But I'm a full-fledged angel now, thank you very much.
하지만 난 이제 정식 천사가 됐어요
The angel radar app didn't sense you. So that was quite a feat.
천사 레이더 앱이 당신을 감지하지 못해서 찾느라 애먹었죠
As you can see, I lost my halo.
너도 알겠지만 난 후광을 잃어버렸어
So there was no way for me to contact Heaven.
그래서 천국에 연락하지 못한 거야
That's why the radar didn't work.
그래서 레이더가 작동 안 했네요
I've been dreaming of this day.
이런 날이 오기를 꿈꿨지
I can finally go back to Heaven now!
난 이제 천국으로 돌아갈 수 있다!
When I go back, I'm gonna relax in a hot bath.
돌아가면 온탕에서 편히 쉴 거야
Nourish myself with nectar and a feast.
과즙 주스와 만찬으로 영양 보충도 해야지
Then I'll fall into a deep sleep in a warm bed.
그러고는 따뜻한 침대에서 깊은 잠에 빠질 거야
What are you waiting for? Take me back to Heaven!
시간 끌 거 없어 날 천국으로 데려가
Good-bye, Pekola.
잘 가라, 페코라
Stop, don't move.
멈춰, 움직이지 마
What's going on?
무슨 일이지?
Here's another one!
다시 또 간다!
Ready? Yakisoba!
준비됐어? 야키소바!
But why?
왜 이러는 거야?
I'm currently serving as your substitute, since you're missing.
네가 행방불명이라 내가 널 대신하고 있지
But if you return, I go back to being an apprentice again.
네가 돌아가면 난 다시 수습 천사가 돼야 해
That'll put an end to my glory days of bossing other angels around.
그러면 다른 천사에게 대장 노릇 하던 내 영광의 날들이 끝나는 거지
I don't follow at all.
전혀 못 알아듣겠어
You're as thick as a brick!
넌 정말 멍청해!
As long as you stay out of Heaven, I'll be treated like royalty!
네가 천국에 오지 않으면 난 왕족처럼 지낼 수 있다고!
So you're not here to bring me back...
넌 날 데리러 온 게 아니구나
I'm here to get rid of you for good.
널 영원히 없애러 왔지
Just when I thought...
집에 돌아갈 거라고
I was about to go home.
생각하자마자
How could this be...?
어떻게 이런 일이...?
I'm so lucky to find you stripped of angel powers.
네가 천사 능력을 뺏겼을 때 널 찾아서 다행이다
Now you're just a piece of meat.
넌 이제 고깃덩어리야
-Meat... -No, more like waste.
- 고기... - 아니지, 쓰레기가 낫다
This is gonna be a piece of cake.
이건 너무 쉽겠어
I always had a feeling she wasn't an angel at heart.
저 애의 본심은 천사 같지 않다는 걸 늘 느꼈지
But this is just ridiculous.
하지만 이건 정말 말도 안 돼
I'm not an angel because I'm worthy of it...
난 가치가 있어서 된 천사가 아니야
I'm an angel because I was born to become one.
난 날 때부터 천사가 되기로 정해져 있었지
Hey, what's up?
어이, 뭐 해?
Is this a bad time?
안 좋은 때인가?
A devil?
악마?
Yurine sent me to deliver this curry to you .
유리네가 이 카레를 네게 갖다 주라고 했어
Curry!
카레다!
But I can't accept charity from a witch.
하지만 난 마녀에게 동정받을 수 없어
-What? You can't eat my curry? -Hey!
- 뭐? 넌 카레를 못 먹어? - 이봐!
-It's out of this world good.
- 이건 끝내주게 맛있어 - 거기!
You're in the way!
내 일을 방해하지 마!
I'll finish you later. Get out of the way!
넌 나중에 없앨 테니 저리 비켜!
You call that curry? It's all potatoes.
저걸 카레라고 하다니 온통 감자밖에 없잖아
Now get out of my sight.
이제 내 눈앞에서 꺼져
Tastes good!
맛있다!
Curry's best the second day.
카레는 이틀째가 제일 맛있어
Day three of simmering in the pot.
냄비에서 3일을 끓였다
Garam masala!
가람 마살라!
Jashin-chan Dropkick!
사신짱 드롭킥!
Die!
죽어!
How could you do that to my curry?
감히 내 카레에 그런 짓을 해?
Waste human lives all you want!
인간 목숨은 얼마든지 버려도 돼
But don't you ever waste precious food!
하지만 귀한 음식은 버려선 안 되는 거다!
-Give me the packing tape! -Okay.
- 포장용 테이프를 줘! - 응
Take that!
받아라!
Kazuyo, this is revenge for breaking up with me.
가즈요, 이건 나를 찬 복수다
WILL
'유서'
Dear God, please forgive me for wasting this life.
신이시여, 이 목숨을 버리는 것을 제발 용서하소서
I don't wanna die! Save me, Mommy!
난 죽고 싶지 않아! 구해줘요, 엄마!
No sight of Poporon...
포포롱이 없어졌네...
Who was that anyway?
그런데 누구였어?
-Oh, well-- -Never mind, I don't care.
- 아, 그게... - 괜찮아, 난 신경 안 써
I'm famished from running so hard.
너무 열심히 달려서 배고프다
Let's go.
가자
Yurine won't believe my story, that a weirdo spilled my curry.
이상한 애가 내 카레를 쏟았다고 하면 유리네가 믿지 않을 거야
Rather than having her send me back out, let's just eat together.
그 애가 날 다시 내보내는 것보다 그냥 같이 먹는 게 낫겠어
But it's a devil's...
하지만 그건 악마의...
Stop making such a fuss. Let's go.
괜히 유난 떨지 말고, 가자
You can't let my curry go to waste.
내 카레는 절대 버리면 안 돼
I hate to admit it, but I was saved by this devil today.
인정하긴 싫지만 오늘 이 악마가 날 구했다
Dropkick on her! Yeah her! I’ll take you down again!
드롭킥을 날린다! 저 애야! 널 다시 무찌를 거다!
Hate you! Love doesn’t exist in this world
네가 싫어! 이 세상에 사랑이란 없어
Fear the dropkick! An Angel looks for her halo
드롭킥을 겁내라! 천사는 후광을 찾는다
As she starves to death!
굶어 죽어가면서 말이야
It’s a love and hate relationship,
이건 애증 관계야
can’t leave each other alone
서로를 가만히 두지 않지
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star!
은하에서 터지는 유성처럼
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and DIE!
천천히, 살금살금 몰래 다가가서 죽인다!
Test my heart, don’t stop
내 마음을 떠봐 멈추지 말고
Let’s go! Dream on! No matter human, angel or devil
가자! 꿈꿔! 인간이건 천사건 악마건
We’re a happy family La la la
우리는 행복한 가족이다 랄랄라
Let me say, I love you!!
내가 말할게 난 널 사랑해!
When all is said and done
모든 것이 끝나면
I’m home! Welcome back, it’s hot pot tonight!
나 왔어! 어서 와, 오늘 밤은 스키야키다!
Come, gather everyone! Let’s enjoy this meal!
모두 어서 모여! 이 요리를 즐기자!
For another crazy tomorrow
내일은 또 정신없을 거야
What next? What next? In the end, Wakeup!
뭔데? 또 뭐지? 결국 깨어나!
A girl constantly hiding her face from the world now walks confidently under the light.
세상에 얼굴을 드러내지 않던 소녀가 이제 밝은 곳에서 당당히 걷는다
However, this happiness did not last long.
하지만 그 행복은 오래 가지 않는다
Dropkick on My Devil! We'll suicide dive into your heart in the next episode too!
사신짱 드롭킥! 다음 화에서도 여러분 가슴에 자살 다이브합니다!